elmotalent.com.au 2017-06-06

# Privacy - ELMO Talent Management Software

## ELMO Talent Management Privacy Policy

ELMO is committed to respecting and protecting the integrity of personal information collected by ELMO to enable us to provide our services. Our policy applies to all users of ELMO software.

This Privacy Policy outlines our practices and rules concerning the handling of your personal information. We will abide by it and the Australian Privacy Principles in force under the Privacy Act ( _Cth_ ) 1988. You may request a printed copy of this Policy, at no charge to you, by contacting us in the manner outlined at the end of this Policy.

This Policy also applies to our associated companies and related businesses including Elmo Talent Management Software Pty Ltd (ACN 605 427 209) and Elmo Learning Services Pty Ltd (ACN 102 455 087).

**Non-personal Information Collected**

ELMO collects non-personal information from website visitors including which sections of the website are navigated and the duration of visits.

**Personal Information Collected**

If you are a Licensee of ELMO’s online talent management software system (Client), we may collect personal information provided by you about individuals within your organisation or seeking to join your organisation. This may include names and contact details such as but not limited to, position titles, addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses. Client data held on ELMO designated servers will remain confidential and only be used for the purposes set out in the license agreement.

If you provide us with personal information about an individual, you warrant to us that you have that person’s consent to disclose their personal information to us, and that your use and disclosure of the information to us is in accordance with all relevant privacy laws.

**Storage & Security of Client Data**

ELMO takes all reasonable steps to ensure the security of client data. Client data is stored on secure servers that are protected in monitored data centres. ELMO employees and contractors are obliged to respect the confidentiality and privacy of the client data.

**Access to Personal Information**

Under the Privacy Act (Cth) 1988, individuals have the right to seek access to personal information stored by ELMO. Individuals have the right to update personal information when it is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

ELMO reserves the right to revise its Privacy policy from time to time. Updated versions of the ELMO Privacy policy will be available on [www.elmotalent.com.au](http://www.elmotalent.com.au/)

**Contact Details**

If you have any questions or feedback about the ELMO Privacy policy, please contact us.

**ELMO Talent Management Software**  
Suite 2502, 520 Oxford Street  
Bondi Junction NSW 2022  
Australia  
Email: [contactus@elmotalent.com.au](mailto:contactus@elmotalent.com.au)  
Phone: 1300 884 510

Last updated on 7 July 2015.
